字幕由电影烧包原创制作 转载请注明
更多精彩电影尽在 www.f-fans.club
林东
Mr. Lin.
- 你女儿情况不太好 - 怎么会这样
- Your daughter's condition is deteriorating - How can that be?
白天不是还好好的吗
She was fine earlier today.
西西的身体优于常人
She heals faster than normal people.
化疗之后
However,
白细胞迅速大量增多
the leukemia cells built up again,
病情突然恶化 西西很坚强
So her condition has deteriorated. But Xixi is strong-willed.
昏迷以前
Before she went into the coma,
她还告诉我们
she told everyone
你答应她 一定会来给她过生日
you'd promised to be there for her birthday.
老吴
Peter.
你一定要把西西救活
You must save her!
我会尽力的 我尽快赶来 全力就她 拜托
I'll do my best. I'm on my way. Please do your best.
让开 让开 对不起
Move, move! Sorry!
- 喂 - 林Sir 证人保护计划出问题了
- Hello? - Officer Lin, we have a problem.
你说什么?
What do you mean?
按计划在原地留守的弟兄们
Our witness protection has been compromised.
刚刚全部失去联系
We just lost contact with our men.
所以我担心现在的藏身地点也已经暴露
I'm afraid our witness has been exposed.
证人保护计划不是刚刚升为A级吗
Witness Protection is Grade A Priority! What are you telling me?
- 出了什么问题? - 还不清楚
- What happened? - I'm not sure,
但是总部刚刚查到这个证人的真实身份
but HQ has comfirmed the identity of the witness.
他就是那个从五角大楼叛逃的基因科学家詹姆斯博士
It's Dr. James, the reclusive geneticist who recently defected.
五年来 他一直在为半岛最大的军火商
For 5 years, he's been secretly working for the region's biggest arms dealer,
做基因生化武器的研究
researching biochemical weapons.
几周前 他研究的生化人基因突变
A week ago, his Bioroid went haywire
将实验室里的所有人全部屠杀
and killed everyone in the lab.
半岛最大的军火商也在家里被残忍肢解
The arms dealer was brutally killed
并抢夺了军火商的所有资产
and his assets seized.
生化人? 这是什么实验?
Bioroid? What research?
具体的细节还不清楚 只知道这些生化人
We don't know the details. It's some kind of
是受到核辐射的特种兵
special force exposed to nuclear radiation.
长官
Sir.
你的编号?
Uniform number?
编号V73
Uniform Number Victor Seven Three.
林特工 总部命令你
Agent Lin, you and your men
立刻带重装备押送证人
are the best guys I've got to transfer Dr. James
转移到地区军事基地
to a secure military base.
如果证人保护失败
The breach of the witness protection plan
可能会危及地区安全
may threaten rigional security.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
- 带走 - 是
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
"林先生 孩子不行了"
"Mr. Lin, the child is dying."
西西...
Xixi...
走
Go!
注意警戒
Keep your eyes open!
相信我 来 快 上车
Trust me. Come on, get in.
撤!
Retreat!
保护博士 隐蔽
Protect Dr. James! Back!
快撤
Get back!
魔鬼...
De...
Devil...
撤
Retreat!
快隐蔽
Take cover!
- 掩护我 - 掩护
- Cover me. - Covering!
- 掩护 - 是
- Cover me! - Yes, sir!
小心
Careful!
小苏 我引开他们 你们上那个装甲车
Susan, I'll distract them. You go for the car!
林sir 林sir
Officer Lin!
- 趴下 - 趴下
- Get down! - Get down!
- 你快带博士突围 - 我也跟你去
- Get Dr. James out of here! - What about you?
快去 保护证人要紧
Just go! Protect the witness first.
- 是 - 闪光弹
- Yes. - Flash bang!
过来 你们几个 跟我走
Come here. You, follow me.
是
Yes, Madam!
- 上装甲车 - 小海 撑着点
- We've got to get to the car! - Johnny, hang in there.
我没事
I'm ok.
小苏 你那边怎么样
Susan, Are you OK?
我们没事
Ok for now.
我们走
Let's go!
不要
No!
不要这样
Don't do this!
不要用这种方式
走
Go.
Go!
快走
Come on!
博士 博士
Doctor, Doctor!
博士中弹
The doctor has been shot.
请求支援
Requesting backup.
Repeat,
博士中弹
The doctor has been shot.
请求支援
Requesting backup.
- 把它给我 - 不不...
- Give it to me. - No, no...
你是一个恶魔
You are a devil.
没有我 你也不能成功
You would have never succeeded without me.
实验记录在哪 他们都是我的
Where are the lab records? They're mine!
再见
Goodbye!
爸爸 爸爸
Papa, Papa.
你还
Hello?
虽然瑞克先生的最新小说还没出版
Although Rick Rogers' latest novel has not yet been published,
其版权就已经成为了好莱坞的抢手货
the copyrights for the movie are already being sought after by Hollywood.
已被天价竞买
Bids for such rights have been coming in at shocking sums.
这本书我已经先睹为快了
I have taken a sneak peek at this book.
她本身就是一种使命 她的血液里记忆着一切
She is a mission herself. Her blood contains all of the memories.
总有一天她会找回记忆
One day, she will find her memories back again.
哇哦
Wow!
我们今晚有幸请到这位贵宾
We are very privileged to welcome to the show
带着他的新书机器之血与大家见面
to talk about his new book BLEEDING STEEL.
有请 瑞克罗杰斯先生
Rick Rogers!
噢 瑞克先生
Oh Rick, oh.
- 你好吗 - 我很好
- How are you? - I'm very well.
欢迎光临我们的节目 谢谢
Welcome to the show, thank you.
请坐
Have a seat.
我们听说书的主角是一个
So we heard the main character was a US marine
受到核辐射死亡的美国特种兵
before he died of nuclear radiation.
后来 他的尸体被一位DNA基因科学家购买
But then, Some geneticists bought his body
将它改造成一个拥有机器心脏的生化人
and turned him into a bioroid with a mechanical heart.
什么都瞒不过你 是吗
Well can't keep a secret from you, can I?
这个世界上可没有什么秘密
There is no secret in this world.
也许是这样的
Maybe that's so.
但是我的小说中存在许多未知的秘密
But many unkown secrets are hidden in my novel.
快买书来看吧
So go buy the book.
是人与机器的完美结合
It's the perfect synergy of the human body and machine.
等等 安全检查
Stop, security check.
转身
Turn around.
我约的小猫咪到了吗?
Is my kitty here yet?
老大 她这就上去
She's on her way, boss.
下一次换我来搜身
Next time, it's my turn.
好吧
Sure.
小猫咪 快过来
Come here, kitty.
到爸爸这来
Come to Papa.
不好意思 你找谁
Excuse me, where are you going?
- 你是谁 - 闭嘴
- Who are you? - Shut up!
你书里的内容哪里来的
Where did you get the information in your book?
到底哪来的
Where did you get the information?
都是我的灵感
It was my inspiration.
你们是什么人
Who are you?
你要干什么
What do you want?
再给你一次机会
This is your last chance.
靠
Shit!
你是谁
Who are you?
机器之血书里的内容是从哪里来的
How did you get the story in BLEEDING STEEL?
- 不要杀我 - 是我买的
- Please don't kill me. - I bought it.
原始素材在哪里
Where's the original copy?
都在那台电脑里 我只是偷了别人的故事
Everything you need is in there. I just stole a story.
混蛋
You shit.
监控画面已经上传完毕 大批警察将到达你的位置
Surveillance videos have been uploaded. A team of policemen are on their way to you.
- 什么情况 - 是蝙蝠侠吗?
- Who is that? - Is that Batman?
著名作家瑞克被谋杀
Popular novelist Rick Rogers has been murdered.
警方之前错误地定性为抢劫
Once police described it as a robbery gone wrong.
我们相信是罪犯故意破坏了大厦的监控画面
We believe the purpose of this criminal disable the CCTV cameras,
然后我们获取到一段
However, we have obtained additional footage.
街角大楼监控拍下的画面
From a CCTV camera in the building on the corner.
警方鼓励市民提供该男子线索
We urges that members of the public who recognize this man step forward.
我们有理由怀疑该男子
We have reason to believe he may have been involved
与本案有关
in the event yhat took place tonight.
我们在瑞克家被一个面具人袭击
We were attacked by a masked man in Rick's apartment.
对不起
I'm sorry.
他很了解我们防弹衣的弱点
He knew a great deal about our bulletproof vests.
你书里的内容哪来的
Where did you get the information in your book?
机器之血里面的内容你是从哪得来的
How did you get the story in BLEEDING STEEL?
- 别杀我 是我买的 - 原始素材在哪里
- Please don't kill me. I bought it. - Where's the original copy?
13年来 你把我像个畜生一样困在这个无菌舱里
13 years you had me trapped in the sterile cage like an animal.
我遭受的痛苦未来一定要你偿还
You gonna suffer everything I've suffered.
我查到了那个异装癖男子
Sir, we found out about the transvestite.
他的衣服是从网上买的
He bought his costume online.
- 我们拿到了收货地址 - 去吧
- We have a shipping address. - Go.
别在让我失望
Do not fail me again.
是的 主人
Yes, sir.
瑞克这个老变态
Rick was a pervert.
干嘛这么关注这个女孩子
Why was he obsessed with this girl?
李森叫的披萨
One pizza for Leeson.
谢谢
Thank you.
当我找到你
When I find you
我要让你死的很难看
I'm gonna kill you.
嗨
Hi.
意大利面?
Spaghetti?
- 是的 谢谢 - 肉酱?
- Yes, please. - Red sauce?
是的
Yeah.
再来点牛肉汤是吧?
And beef soup, right?
- 谢谢 先生 - 给这个漂亮的女孩来碗牛肉汤
- Thank you, sir. - Beef soup for the beautiful young lady.
- 对不起 - 婊子
- Sorry. - Bitch.
不好意思
Excuse me?
你说什么
What did you say?
- 对不起 我听不懂 - 你的中式英语
- Sorry, I can't really understand you. - I don't speak Chinglish.
你够狠
That's good one.
哎哟
Oops.
你做过隆鼻手术吗
Have you had a nose job?
什么?
What?
- 对不起 - 别打了 别打了
- I'm sorry. - No more, no more.
退后 算了 算了
Back off! Back off!
别打了
Let it go. Enough, let it go.
- 顾念冷静点 - 算了 算了 算了
- Back it off, girl. - It's ok, drop it.
散了 散了
Get back, get back,
没什么好看的
nothing to see.
你刚才简直太帅了 太给我们华人长脸了
That was a hell of a punch. You're a credit to us Chinese.
- 我刚刚有帮你 看到了吗 - 谢谢
- And you know I helped, right? - Thanks.
我还要上课 我先走了
Well I have to go now.
我叫李森 怎么称呼啊?
I'm Leeson, what's your name?
南希
Nancy!
你还好吗 你又做噩梦了吗
Are you ok? Did you have another nightmare?
- 喝点水 - 谢谢
- Drink something. - Thank you.
我又把你吵醒了
Did I wake you again?
对不起
I'm sorry.
自从我换了医生以后
Ever since I changed doctors,
情况比以前更糟了
the nightmares have gotten worse.
因为她不是一个医生
Because that's not a doctor.
她是个女巫
She's a witch.
她不是一个真正的女巫
She's not like a real witch.
她更像是一个指引者
She's more like a guide
或者说是灵媒之类的
or a spiritualist or something.
好吧 不管她是什么
OK, whatever she is
我的噩梦变的更可怕 更清晰了
the dreams are getting worse and clearer.
你现在每晚都做噩梦
You have them every night.
我再也受不了了 看我都瘦成这样了
I can't take it any more. I've lost my weight.
根本睡不好觉
And I can't sleep.
求你了 南希 别再去找那个女巫了
Please, Nancy, stop going to the witch,
要不就让她治好你
or get her to fix it.
你好
Hello
- 看过来 - 你好
- look over. - Hello.
你叫什么名字
What's you name?
宝贝 我等你好久了
Come on, baby. I've been waiting for you for ages.
最近感觉怎么样
How've you been?
那些噩梦更加频繁 也更清晰
The nightmares are more frequent and more vivid.
在梦里我变成了另一个人
I feel like I become someone else in my dreams.
治疗还需要时间
It takes time to heal.
亲爱的 这是压力太大
This is stress, my dear.
出现的幻象 没事的
Figments of your imagination. Nothing more.
但是梦境特别真实
But every bit of it feels so real.
像是我去过那个地方 认识那些人
Like I've been there, and I know all those people.
就像是
As if
有人在指引我 去寻找什么
they are leading me, pushing me to find something.
你不要想太多 放松
Don't think too much. Relax.
一...
One...
二...
Two...
三...
Three...
博士 实验体排异强烈
Doctor, the subject is rejecting multiple organs.
各器官出现衰竭
They are failing.
那就放弃吧
I think we gonna have to give up on this one.
- 南希 不... - 救救我
- Nancy! No... - Help me!
不要杀我
Please don't kill me.
- 南希... - 不要杀我
- Nancy... - Don't kill me.
杀了我 更没有人可以救你
If you kill me, nothing can save you.
怎么回事...?
What the fuc...?
我从没见过你这样的病症
I've never seen anything like this before.
你身体里一定不止一个灵魂
There's someone else's soul inside you.
我真的帮不了你了
This is way beyond me now.
有一个人
There's a man.
他是顶级催眠大师
He is a master of hypnosis.
他应该可以帮到你
He might help.
明天他会在这里
He will be there tomorrow.
看你是否能见到他
Let's see if you can see him.
你怎么就让她走了 她还没告诉我们她的梦
Why did you let her go? She hasn't told us anything about her dream.
针断两半了
The needle broke in half.
瑞克已经死了
Rick's dead.
我有一种预感
I have a feeling
我们卖给他的录像
the tapes we were selling him,
和他的死有关
got him into trouble.
看这是谁 我看你经常来这
See what we have here. I see you come here a lot.
找那个骗子巫师 你叫什么名字
Looking at that lame witch. What's your name?
那是我哥们
Now that's my boy.
安德拉
Antara.
- 让我过去 - 原来你会说英文
- Let me pass. - So now you speak English?
这怎么样
How about this?
从这爬过去 我知道你肯定喜欢
Pass under here I know you like that, huh?
抓住她
Get that bitch!
伙计们 过来 捉到一个新鲜货
Come on, boys. We got fresh meat.
别害怕
Don't be soared.
走开
Back off.
- 走开 - 别靠近我
- Back off! - Don't get close!
喔 这下惨了
Oops.
这是个辣妞
Feisty one.
现在你跑不掉了
You can't get away now.
好吧
Okay.
你以为你是成龙啊
Who you think you are, Jackie Chan?
快走
Let's go!
- 站住 - 坏蛋
- Stop! - You bastard!
快
Come on!
- 我感觉我快瞎了 - 别让这个小婊砸跑了
- Shit, I think I'm blind. - Don't let that bitch slip away!
站住 别跑
Stop running!
别跑 你害我断子绝孙
I will get you! You broke my balls.
关门啊 快 快
Shut the door. Hurry up!
我们好像见过
I think we've met before.
- 是你啊 - 你怎么会在这里
- Oh, it's you. - What are you doing here?
- 我跟踪你啊 - 为什么跟踪我
- I followed you. - Why did you do that?
我开玩笑的
I was kidding.
你做什么的
So who are you?
黑社会啊?
Gangster?
- 什么 - 你怎么老是跟别人打架
- Excuse me? - You're always getting into fights.
去哪啊
Hey, hey.
别生气啦 跟你开个玩笑嘛
Come on, relax. I was kidding.
你先别走嘛
Don't go.
等一下啦
Come on.
那个 我们晚上一起吃个饭吧
Let's go for dinner tonight.
你还是回家换条裤子吧
I think you should cahnge your pants.
裤子?
Pants?
也好
Yeah.
晚上刚好
Well, yeah.
我也有事
Whatever.
我警告你 以后不要再跟踪我
I'm warning you. If you follow me again,
小心我...
then I'll...
我哪有跟踪你 我都说这是开玩笑的
Follow you? I said I was kidding.
这是偶遇 偶遇啊
This was just a coincidence, all right?
我刚刚救了你 谢都不用谢的啊
Not even a thank you for saving you?
- 你怎么这样子啊 - 谢谢
- You know what, lady? - Thank you.
很没礼貌呀
You're welcome.
嗨
Hey.
你好 我要找一位演员
Excuse me, I'm looking for a performer.
演员?
A performer?
他们正在排练 表演晚上才开始
They are in rehearsal right now. The performance is in the evening.
我需要现在见他 有急事
I need to see him right now. It's urgent.
抱歉 没有同行证 不能让你进去
I'm sorry, I can't let you in without a permit.
好吧 谢了
Ok, thank you.
嗨
Hi.
哥们儿 她是我女朋友
Hey guys, She's my girlfriend.
能让她进来吗?
Can she come in?
- 进吧 - 谢谢
- Should be alright. - Thank you.
嗨 宝贝
Hey baby.
走
Come on.
我女朋友
My girlfriend.
你又跟踪我
You followed me again.
我跟踪你? 我比你先到这里的
I followed you? What are you talking about?
要不是我你进的来吗?
And who just goy you in?
懒得理你
Whatever.
你去哪 那边是后台
You can't... Not that way!
嗨
Hi.
这里跟迷宫一样 别乱跑
It's a maze in here, Where are you going?
你叫什么名字啊
What's your name?
黑社会
Gangster.
我昨天跟你开玩笑的 你不要介意嘛
Come on. You know I was kidding yesterday Forget it, all right?
你呢?
Yours?
我上次跟你说过了 李森
Don't you remember? I told you. It's Leeson.
"默罕默德 香肠"
"Mohammed Salaami."
- 那是艺名 - 偷的吧
- It's my stage name. - Stolen?
当然不是
It was not.
抱歉
Sorry.
是捡的
I found it.
一看就不像这里的工作人员
You sure don't look like Salaami.
找什么
What are you after?
你在找什么
What are you looking for?
默罕默德 香肠
Mohammed Salaami.
香肠 是的 我是香肠
Salaami. Yeah, I'm Salaami.
香肠 香肠
Salaami.
- 香肠 - 好 找到你太好了
- Salaami! - Good, I am glad I found you.
- 你得跟我过来一下 - 去干嘛啊
- I need you come with me. - Where are we going?
- 我需要你调整一下灯光 - 好 好 好
- I need you to fix some lights. - OK, OK, OK.
乖乖等我啊 不要乱跑啊
Just stay here. Please just stay there.
不要再打架啊
No more fighting.
听到没
OK?
香肠
Salaami.
好的 各位 咱们开始准备排练
OK, everybody. Let's start rehersal.
灯光 乐手 就位
Lights, music, get ready.
好了 准备 开始
OK, ready? Action!
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
各位观众 下面有请世界顶级催眠大师科森蒂诺
Please welcome Mr. Cosentino.
女士们先生们 今晚你们即将目睹精彩绝伦的表演
Ladies and gentlemen, what you're about to see tonight is trult extraordinary.
我的天使已经来到
My angel has arrived.
到我这来
Come to me.
请坐
Sit down.
你本是坠入凡间的天使
You were a fallen angel,
上帝给了你第二次生命
but God has given you a second life.
我知道你所有的痛苦
I know all your pain.
我愿引领你 走出黑暗 见到光明
I'll guide you through the darkness to the light.
找回那个原本属于你的灵魂
And find the soul that belongs to you.
爱始终在你身边
Love is all around you.
- 不 不 不要杀我 - 大家快逃
- No, no... please. - Everybody get out!
快 快 快...
Go, go, go...
不要滥杀无辜
Stop, jangan budon't kill the innocent people.
我去看看
I got this.
你来晚了
You are late.
我的使命完成了
My work here is done.
- 放下武器 - 趴下
- Put your weapons down! - Get on the ground!
小心啊
Look out!
抓住他
Get him!
杀了他
Kill him.
南希在右侧二楼
Nancy's on the second floor.
带我到出口
Take me up to the entrance.
你真的惹毛我了
You know you are really starting to piss me off.
把女儿还给我
Give me back my daughter.
你想要她? 暂时给你保管
You want her? She's all yours, daddy.
抱歉
Sorry.
喂 开过来
Hey! Over here!
大叔 你跟她什么关系啊
Mister, who are you to her?
闭嘴
Shut up.
哇 大叔 你家...
Wow, nice place. Is it...
你干嘛
Hey.
- 你铐我干嘛 - 别吵
- What the hell? - Be quiet.
你铐我...
Let go of me.
- 走 - 去哪?
- Go. - Where?
- 下去 - 我不要
- Down there. - No way.
- 下去 - 你要干嘛
- Go down there! - What do you want?
你要杀人灭口啊
You trying to get rid of me?
这到底什么地方啊
What the hell is this place?
大叔
Hey.
慢一点嘛
Watch it, Take it easy.
这么多枪啊
Oh my God.
大叔 你到底是干嘛的
Who are you? What do you do for a living?
你为什么把我铐起来?
Do you really need to do that?
你要干嘛
What the hell?
你给我吃什么东西啊
What was that thing anyhow?
定时炸弹
It's a time bomb.
说吧 你为什么一直跟踪南希
Tell me. Why have you been following Nancy?
你人怎么这样子啊
You've got to be kidding.
这是我们男人之间的竞争
It's between us men.
泡妞是凭魅力 你吃醋也没有必要杀人灭口吧
I can't help it if I'm super charming. You don't have to kill me to get my girl!
你根本不是悉尼大学的大学生
You're not a student at the university.
在瑞克家戴假发扮女人的
The transvestite at Rick's place.
- 就是你 - 对 我承认那是我
- It was you? - Yes, it's true.
可是我不明白整件事情跟南希什么关系啊
But what does any of this have to do with Nancy?
我扮女人只是想拿回属于自己的东西
All I did is get back what was mine to begin with.
属于你的东西?
What belongs to you?
- 什么东西 - 有钱人的东西
- What was it? - Things that belong to the rich.
劫富济贫 你懂吗
I'm like Robin Hood, okay?
那叫贼
It's stealing.
年轻人不努力 学别人偷东西
You lazy young boy, you're just a thief.
瑞克也不是什么好东西 他也一样是贼
Rick is a dick. And he's also a thief.
这与你纠缠南希有什么关系
What does that have to do with Nancy?
我洗劫瑞克保险柜的时候
When I was going through Rick's safe,
恰好里面有张南希在图书馆的借书卡
Nancy's library pass was in there.
我就好奇这个女生什么来路了
I was curious about her.
后来我就看着看着
And then she just..
不小心 就爱上她了
Captivated me. And I fell in love.
完毕
Over.
该说的我都说完了
I've told you everthing.
你不可以把炸弹...
Would you please...
- 一直储存在我肚子里吧 - 维生素B
- remove the bomb now? - Vitamin B.
对身体好的 还能解酒
Good for your health, and for hangovers.
你耍我啊 你到底是什么人啊
You fooled me. Who the hell are you?
你整天戴着面具飞来飞去飞来飞去的
I could tell it was you flying around under that mask.
你当你是蜘蛛侠啊 吐丝啊
Who do you think you are, Spiderman? Shoot a web!
在没有确实你身份之前 不能离开这里
Until I confirm your identity you'll have to stay here.
你放开我
Let me out!
林sir 你查到的银行账单
Officer Lin, the bank records are obtained
的确是瑞克和女巫之间的交易记录
are proof of transactions between Rick and the witch.
这两年 瑞克定期向女巫购买南希的治疗录像
For 2 years, the wich has been selling Rick Nancy's therapy videos.
因此我判断 小说里的内容也是来源于此
Clearly, Rick based his novel off these recordings.
跟我想到的差不多
That's what I thought.
对了 我刚发了份录音给你
Oh, I just sent you a sounf file.
帮我查查他的真实身份
Find that who that guy is.
好
Ok.
你好
Hello?
你到底要把我关到什么时候啊
Hey, How long are you going to keep me looked up here?
还有没有人权啊
I have human rights.
你再不放开我可要尿尿了 我尿了啊
I'll pee if you don't let me go. Ok, you asked for it.
我真要尿了啊
I'm going to pee now!
你总得给我弄点吃的喝的吧
Can you give me water and food please?
我现在连尿都尿不出来了
I'm so dehydrated. I can't even pee.
一定要保护好她
She must be protected.
我毕生的心血都在她身体里
All my work is in her body.
终有一天她会帮我向世界证明
Someday she'll be the proof to the world
我对人类的贡献
of my contribution to mankind.
- 喂 南希不见了 - 林sir
- Hello? Nancy's gone. - Officer Lin.
我刚刚查到她上了一班新赣的飞机
She just got on plane to Xingan.
我担心的事情终于发生了
The thing I've been afraid if is finally happening.
我去找她
I'm going to get her.
- 好 - 到了机场我跟你联络
- OK - I'll call you from the airport.
- 收到 - 南希不见了? 放开我啊
- Copy that. - What happened? Release me.
我们去就她啊
Look, I can help you.
不管你的目的是什么
Whatever your game is,
以后不准靠近南希 这个事情比你想像的更严重
stay away from her. This is more serious than tou know.
- 我是在保护她 - 她不需要你保护
- I want to protect her. - She doesn't need you.
拿着钥匙 这个防爆门明天自动会打开
Here's the key. The door will open automatically tomorrow.
房间里吃的喝的都有 饿不死你
There's food and drink in the room. You won't starve.
不是这个 是那个
That's dog food. There.
练好你的臂力
Train your arms.
你这是非法拘禁
This is an illega detention.
大叔
Hey!
地震啊
Erathquake?
林sir 这是你们的新身份
Officer Lin, Your new identity.
旧档案里
The old flies
你跟西西都是死亡
stayed with you when Xixi died.
博士的尸体...
And Dr. James' body,
我已经处理妥善了
we had it taken care of.
死前他用机械心脏和基因血
He managed to save Xixi with mechanical heart
救活了西西
and bioengineered blood.
现在西西成了博士
Inside Xixi's body,
DNA移植的母体
are the bioengineered genes that of Dr. James.
目前没有出现任何排异
So far no sign of rejection.
西西身体里的生物基因血
The bioengineered blood in Xixi's body
有着超强的再生能力
is super regenerative.
只是等她醒来之后
However, when she wakes up,
她生前所有的记忆都会被消除
her old memories will be gone.
...也包括你
Including... memories of you.
被我炸死的那个...
What's that thing that I blew up?
是不是生化人?
The bioroid?
是
Yes.
他是詹姆斯博士的试验品 叫安德烈
He was an exprimental subject. Dr. James called him Andre.
我们的人在爆炸现场 没有找到他的尸体
His body wasn't recovered at the scene.
目前仍在继续搜索
We are still searching...
小苏
Susan.
- 林sir - 能不能帮我一个忙
- Yes, sir. - Can you do me a favor?
您说
Of course.
把她带到澳洲孤儿院
Take her to an orphanage in Australia,
交给伊莎贝拉院长
To director Isabella.
好
OK.
安德烈 一定会回来找我的
Andre, will definitely come back.
我不想西西收到牵连
I don't want Xixi to be involved.
只要女儿好好的活着
As long as she lives,
我以陌生人的身份守在她身边
I will protect her as a stranger.
也就无欲无求了
As a father, her safety is all i ask for.
林sir 你说西西现在自己跑回来
Officer Lin, if Xixi's memories are coming back,
她恢复的记忆是自己的
are they hers
还是詹姆斯博士的?
or are they Dr. James'?
我也在担心这个问题
That's what I worry about.
喔 对了 我叫你查那个人查的怎么样
Oh yeah, what about the guy I asked you to check out?
查到了 李森
His name is Leeson.
十五年前定居悉尼
He lives in Sydney.
2011年出境前往美国
In 2011, he travelled to the US.
韩国 中国和日本等地
Korea, China, and Japan
两年前返回悉尼
and then returned to Sydney 2 years ago.
一直没有工作记录 也没有查到他家人任何信息
He has no work records, no family we could find.
一年前他因为涉嫌盗窃被捕
He was arrested for theft a year ago.
但是因为证据不足 他很快就被释放了
But was released due to lack of evidence.
他盗窃什么呢
What did he steal?
不知道 他的档案被人加密
We don't know. His file is classified.
我们和澳洲警方...
We are still communicating with the
还在继续沟通中
Australian Police.
他绝对不是一个普通的盗贼
He's not a normal thief.
我也觉得他没有那么简单
No. We don't think so either.
西西的定位一直被干扰 我们需要分头行动
We're losing Xixi's signal. I think we should separate.
那我马上回总部 立刻启动第二套计划
Ok. I'll return to headquarters and initiate Plan B.
总部希望这次任务结束之后
We will do everything we can
可以恢复你的身份
to have your identity restored.
如果可以找到西西 我更希望跟她过平静的生活
If I can find Xixi, I just want to have a peaceful life with her.
- 分头行动吧 - 林sir...
- See you. - Sir...
多加小心啊
Good luck, Officer Lin.
相信我
Trust me.
你好
Hello.
我毕生的研究成果都在她身体里 她的血液里记录这一切
All my work is in her body. Every detail is recorded in her blood.
一定要好好保护她
She must be protected.
终有一天她会帮我向世界证明我对人类的贡献
Someday she'll be the proof to the world of my contribution to mankind.
爸爸...
Papa...
原来你一直在我身边
You've been with me all along.
爸爸...
Papa...
爸爸
Papa!
西西
Xixi!
爸爸
Papa!
我没有时间陪他玩
I don't have time for this.
完蛋去
Go to hell!
哎呀我滴个妈呀 这网上学的招还真管用
Oh my God! It workedl!
大叔 你跟错车啦
Hey, You chased the wrong car.
你是怎么跑出来的
How did you get out?
你那个拉力器对我根本不算什么
A fitness machine is no match for me.
你这么有本事 你帮我找到他们
If you're that good, help me find them.
都什么年代了 我们都是外地人嘛
Come on, it's the 21st century. We're not locals.
一定会用导航
So we've gotta use GPS.
等等啊
Hang on.
你没用啦 回悉尼
Good job. Go back to Sydney.
还回悉尼啊 我差点被你炸死
What? You almost blew me up!
- 你这个猪队友 - 南希被他们抓了
- Go on then. - They've got Nancy.
我已经把她的位置发到你手机上面
I'm sending you a location.
- 收到 我们立即行动 - 好
- Got it, let's move! - OK.
下午好 有什么可以帮您
Good afternoon. May I help you?
请稍等一下
Please wait a minute.
老公老公 你看
Honey, look.
三个外星人
Three aliens.
谢谢
Thank You.
请走这边
This way please.
不不不不... 混蛋
NO, no, no, no... bastard!
行动
Let's roll!
这边这边
Turn here.
- 小苏 - 上车
- Susan? - Get in.
这个方法很好
Brilliant idea.
我真的不想再看见有人牺牲
I don't want to see more people get hurt.
我对13年前被我们打死的黑衣人进行研究
I did a study of the men in black we killed 13 years ago.
发现他们生化服发呼吸系统漏洞很大
And discovered that their suits are susceptible to gas.
这次 正好被我们利用上
Now, we're just exploiting that weakness.
- 长官 - 怎么样
- Madam. - How was it?
已经对保险箱进行了彻底搜查
This is what we found in the safe.
- 里面只有这个 - 只有台DV?
- Noting else. - Just a camera?
- 好 警戒 - 是
- OK. - Yes.
这种超强的再生能力
Such superior regeneration ability
是因为来自海星的再生基因被激活
is attributed to the activation of the regenerative genes from the starfish.
每一个重组细胞中 都包含着整个基因组
Each recombined cell contains the entire genom,
并和其他组织融合 快速生长出失去的所有部分
and fuses to other tissue to rapidly regrow the missing part.
这个实验体是一名受到严重核辐射感染的特种兵
The experimental subject is a special force exposed to heavy nuclear radiation.
如果实验成功 他将成为世界上第一个生化战士
He'll become the first bio-warrior in the world if the experiment succeeds.
为了匹配基因血的快速生长特性
We have developed the first generation mechanical heart
我们研制出第一代机器心脏
to match the rapid regeneration feature of the bioengineered blood.
如果实验成功
If the experiment succeeds,
拥有机器心脏和基因血的生化人
the bioroid with the mechanical heart and the bioengineered blood,
将成为未来世界的不死战士
will be the immortal warrior of the future.
这个实验记录要是被他拿到的话
If Andre gets his hands on the lab records,
那他就可以制造更多像他那样的生化人
he can create an army of bioroids just like him.
那简直太可怕的吧
That's horrifying.
这决不能被安德烈拿到
We can't let Andre get this.
总部调查到去年安德烈和R国军火商
According to our intel, Andre had a secret deal with
开始了一项秘密合作
a prominant arms dealer.
我怀疑 这很有可能就是他们迫切需要的成果
I bet, this is what they were working on together.
可是 目前只有这个东西才能换回南希
But, this is the only thing we have that we can trade for Nancy.
就算他拿到这个 安德烈也绝不会放过南希
No matter what, he won't release Nancy.
林sir 十三年前
Officer Lin, 13 years ago
安德烈被你炸伤之后 他的身体受到严重感染
Andre was hurt. His body was severely infected
这么多年 他被困在无菌仓里不能出来
and for all these years he's been kept confined in a sterile room.
所以他迫切的需要南希身上成功的基因血去解救他
What he needs is Nancy's blood to save himself.
这个和南希都是他需要的
This and Nancy are the two things he needs.
只要他没拿到实验记录
So long as we still have the lab records,
南希就是安全的
Nancy should be safe.
时间不多了 得先找到安德烈再说
We don't have much time. We have to find Andre.
我有办法了
I have an idea.
DV呢?
Where's the camera?
马上将DV安全送到总部
Take this camera straight to Headquarters.
是的 长官
Yes, Madam.
老板 他们回来了
Boss, they are back.
你和我 其实是同类
You and I, are actually the same.
都是实验室里的小白鼠
We are lab rats in his little experiment.
只是你没有经历过我所经历的
The only difference is you didn't get to experience
那些痛苦
the pain I have suffered.
没想到这老狐狸
That sly fox
把他第二代实验成果
hiding his life's work
给了你
inside of you.
这么多年
And all these years,
为了苦苦找你
just to find you.
我感觉是你把我变成了怪物
I feel like you've turned me into a monster monster.
分离器启动 净化开始
Diverter initiated, Purification in process.
你们是谁
Who are you?
我们同样拥有机器心脏
We have the same mechnanical heart.
可我身体里这些不成功的细胞不断吞噬着我
But I am getting eaten alive by my own cells.
现在有了詹姆斯博士成熟的基因血
Thanks to Dr. James' blood
我不仅可以恢复我原本的超能力量
not only will i get my powers back,
而且你的血液可以给我再生的能力
but your blood will give me the ability to regenerate.
世界上第一个不死的生化战士
The world's first super bio-warrior.
我的身体里 13年来一直存在着两个人的血液
My blood contains two sets of memories for 13 years.
那些混乱的记忆时刻折磨着我
Those painful memories constantly tortured me day by day.
你将会有三个人的记忆
You will have three memories
一旦我的血液输给你
once I pass them onto you.
相信我
And believe me
那些混乱的记忆会把你逼疯
you will go insane.
不会的
No.
你看到这个分流器了么
You see this diverter here?
它会过滤掉你血液里的所有记忆
It'll remove all the memories sin your blood.
我绝不会再经历任何痛苦
Never again will I experience any more pain.
你查到什么啦
What's that?
跟你没关系
Quiet down.
实验室在二楼
The lab's on the second floor.
走
Let's go.
- 那个亚洲女孩在哪 - 在实验室里
- Where is the asian girl? - Inside the lab.
开门
Open the door.
你们是什么人
What are you guys doing?
- 南希 - 你不能靠近那边
- Nancy! - Where do you think you're going?
- 肖恩... - 赶快报警
- Shaun... - Sound the alarm!
快离开这里 大家快跑
Get out of here! Go, go, go, go!
南希
Nancy!
- 这鬼东西怎么打开呀 - 南希
- How do we open this?? - Nancy!
这鬼东西怎么打开呀
How do we get in?
躲开
Get back.
- 怎么没有用啊 - 不管用
- It doesn't work. - How can that be?
爸爸
Papa...
- 把门打开 - 只有老板能开
- Open it now! - Only the boss can do that.
阿西吧
Fuck!
是我是我 我刚才想帮你们的
It's me, It's me! I was trying to help.
后来发现枪没电了
But my gun was out of power.
我会慢慢享受杀你的过程
I'll enjoy killing you.
我数到三 我们一起上
On three, we attack.
我还没数
I haven't started counting!
血液传输中断 开始回流
Blood transfusion interrupted, Reverting.
再见
Goodbye!
- 快来帮忙 - 好
- Come and help me! - OK.
去死
Go to hell!
警告 系统故障
Warning, System malfunctioning.
爸爸小心
Watch out, Papa!
所有人紧急撤离
All personnel evacuate.
警告 系统故障
Warning, System malfunctioning.
所有人紧急撤离
All personnel evacuate.
警告 系统故障
Warning, System malfunctioning.
- 爸爸 - 大叔
- Papa! - Uncle!
林sir
Officer Lin!
- 爸爸 - 这里要爆炸了 快跑
- Papa! - It's going to explode! Run!
快 快
Run! Hurry!
所有人紧急撤离
All personnel evacuate.
- 快走 - 李森
- Go! - Leeson!
- 走 - 李森
快走啊
Go, Hurry!
要坠机啦 快穿降落伞
It's going to crash! Get the parachutes!
好
OK.
- 爸爸 - 爸爸没事
- Papa. - Papa's fine.
你不要怕 小苏
Don't worry. Susan!
快帮她穿上
Strap her.
再也不要离开我了
Don't ever leave me alone again.
- 爸爸 - 林sir
- Papa! - Officer Lin!
快带她 走
Get her out of here! Go!
爸爸 爸爸 等我病好了
Papa, Papa. When I get well,
你答应过我要去游乐园玩哦
you've promised you'll take me to an amusement park.
我生命的时间不多了
I don't have much time left.
我吧我最成功的生物基因血全部给了西西
The bioengineered blood of my biggest sucess was all given to Xixi.
这些血液拥有着超强的再生能力
It has superior regeneration capabilities.
一定要保护好她
Take good care of her.
- 林sir - 爸爸
- Officer Lin! - Papa!
小苏姐 快想办法救我爸爸
Susan, do something. Save him.
左边有个黑色把手 我叫你拉就拉
Pull the black handle on your left when I tell you to.
好
OK.
拉
Now!
- 爸爸 - 西西
- Papa! - Xixi!
爸爸
Papa!
- 别怕 - 你的手没事了? - 没事了
- Don't be afraid! - How is your arm? - I'm OK.
苏sir DV机里的实验记录不见了
Madam, the lab records are missing.
什么? 实验记录不见了?
What? The lab records are gone?
比个耶 我在录影了
Cheese. Recording now.
在录了
Smile at the camera.
等会我们去玩那个
Let's try that one.
老爸 我爱你
I love you, Daddy.
- 好开心啊 - 我都晕了
- I am so happy! - I'm dizszy.
老爸
Daddy!
老爸 我们去玩那个
I'm dizzy. Let's try that one.
哪一个
Which one?
- 那个 那个 老爸 - 不行不行 我心脏受不了
- That one. - No, no, no... My heart can't...
- 爸爸 - 西西
- Please. - Xixi.
- 我陪你玩 那是我最爱 - 那好吧
- I'll go, I like that one. - Alright!
你们找个地方休息一下
You go get some rest.
我去给你们买超级好吃的冰淇淋
I'm going to get you guys some fantastic ice cream.
- 我要巧克力口味的 - 好的
- I'll have chocolate. - OK.
我要坐一坐
I need to sit down.
快找个地方坐一下 那
Let's find a place to sit down. Over there.
我是倒坐着给你们拍的
I was shooting..like this, backwards.
我就知道你会晕
I knew you'd be dizzy.
好像做梦一样 你掐我一下
This all feels like a dream. Pinch me.
我可不掐你 一掐你就醒了
I won't do that. You'll wake up.
林sir 你等这一天 等了13年啊
Officer Lin, You've been waiting for this for 13 years.
我真为你高兴
I'm so happy for you.
林sir 刚刚总部来电话了
Officer Lin, Headquarters just called.
说李森的身份已经查明
We know Lesson's true identity.
他的真实姓名叫崔京浩
His real name is Choi Kyung-ho.
他的父亲就是13年前被安德烈分尸的半岛军火商
His father was the arms dealer killed 13 years ago by Andre.
哦 原来这小子的真实目的是来报仇的
So his motivation was to get revenge.
顺便拿回他的家产
And take back his family's assets.
我扮女人只是想拿回属于自己的东西
All I did is get back what was mine to begin with.
安德烈杀他全家的时候 他正巧在国外
When his family was killed, he was traveling abroad.
所以躲过了一劫
So he survived.
不过很巧合的是 他跟西西
Coincidentally, he and Xixi
在同一个孤儿院生活过
grew up together in the orphanage.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
祝南希生日快乐
Happy birthday to Nancy
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
南希 祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday, Nancy.
李森
Leeson.
Leeson!
价格不是问题
Price is not a problem.
我对你手里实验记录录像带很感兴趣
If you've got for me what you said din the e-mail.
到我办公室来
Come over ro my office in Moscow.
我们聊聊
We'll talk.
我可以派私人飞机去接你
I can send a olane to come get you.
嗨 兄弟
Hey, man.
谢谢你愿意跟我合作
Thanks for openly discussing a price.
不过我听说你是个不守信用的人
Although... it's a matter of trust.
不好意思了 我晚上要和成龙吃饭 拜拜
Sorry, I have a dinner date with Jackie Chan later.
拜拜
Over.
妈的
Fuck!